Hello, everyone.
Welcome to today's
Incomplete Summer Party Night.
I'm Sun Mingyang, your host for today.
Thank you, thank you all.
Tonight we'll have
all kinds of amazing games.
Let's welcome our first guest of the night,
shall we?
Let's give a big round of applause to
Jiang Xiaomeng.
Zhou Guorui.
Ma Weixian.
Welcome.
Welcome, our beach jock.
What a great figure.
Chen Zhixuan.
Wang Ruijian.
Summer beach style.
Mr. Bai Ganyu.
Let's welcome our Bai Guanyu.
Zhang Ziyu.
Let's welcome
the Rocking Panda.
Okay, DJ, give us a beat.
You're a snake, right?
Who's up for a belly dance?
Come on, you go then.
Let's take turns to battle, okay?
We'll take turns.
Taking turns, that okay?
Battle.
Then I'll do some street dance too.
B-Boy.
How embarrassing.
Next.
Why did you bump into me?
Full-on confrontation.
So who's teaming up with whom?
Come on, spin around.
Let's do the
musical climax.
Can you dance?
Let's all dance together at the musical climax.
I'll go.
Can you teach us a move?
It's total chaos in here.
Totally freestyling, buddy.
Come early.
Zhang Ziyu, it's one against seven!
You should've shown it earlier.
Cool.
Yeah!
Welcome, students,
to our pajama party!
A party's gotta have games.
So, the trainee who wins today's game
will get a large pack of snacks.
I love games with prizes.
Now let's play our first game.
Human Conveyor Belt.
Eight students draw body parts in turn.
You must pass the tennis ball
using the body part you drew.
The last student
needs to put the tennis ball into that plate.
During the passing process
if the ball drops, we start over.
If we get it across in five minutes,
we win.
What?
Wait, what if it's mouth-to-butt?
You can decide the order among yourselves.
I'll go last, then.
I'll take the hardest job.
Don't stand next to Mingyang. What if he draws a foot?
He's not wearing socks.
I want to be here.
I'll be second to last.
Get outta here.
Get over there.
Then you with Mingyang.
Why me?
I want to be here.
After we decide the order,
let's draw the body parts you'll use.
What if it's butt?
Mouth.
Collarbone.
Face.
Face for me too.
Elbow.
Foot.
Elbow to foot.
Using elbows and feet is easier.
Let me tell you.
Be careful.
Don't make me use my mouth.
Mouth.
Any more mouths left?
I'm the mouth.
Butt.
That works.
Any more mouths left, Director?
What if Mingyang is the mouth later?
Let's see what the butt pairs with.
Chest.
Chest to butt.
I'm the chest, that works.
Alright, let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
Your mouth.
It's fine.
Come on, a little closer.
Smooth.
First round, smooth.
Very smooth.
Come on.
Take a look.
Good.
Second round went smoothly too.
Come on.
What good is a smooth start?
Come on, don't move.
I'll turn my body.
Come on.
Bro.
Don't move.
Stop laughing.
Relax.
Relax, don't move.
Good, clamp it.
I've got it.
Got it, huh?
Are you sure that counts as clamping it?
Okay.
Between the two thighs,
that part counts as the butt, right?
Come on, spread your legs.
He's taking his pants off.
Don't move.
Wait, my toes are about to cramp, guys!
Come on, start from the top.
What a shame, we'll need another ball.
Only four balls.
Only four chances.
Only four balls, buddies.
First the mouth, then the chest,
then the butt, then the foot.
Keep going.
Keep it going.
Come on.
So passing one ball counts as a win?
Right.
Here it comes.
Come on.
Why is there water on this ball?
Put it somewhere higher on him.
It's easier for me to catch.
My toes are about to cramp.
Mingyang, hurry up.
Good.
Nice.
How about this?
Just pick him up.
The egg has dropped.
Not easy.
No need for me to go again.
Good. Of course, that was just a warm-up.
For our next round,
we'll swap the balls for ice cubes.
Wait.
Can I draw another one?
Then we'll just have to pick again.
What about my butt?
Pick a new one.
The order's staying the same, right?
Change it.
Okay.
You can change it now.
Good. Starting with Sun Mingyang.
Drawing lots.
Chest.
Why is it chest again?
You and the chest are just fated.
Not bad.
Using my chest is no problem for me.
Why do I feel like I'm the butt
What if it's feet again?
Collarbone.
Butt.
Collarbone to butt is fine too.
Then what about Zhang Ziyu?
Come on, Zhang Ziyu, go choose one.
Elbow. Not bad. Elbow.
That's easy.
The first four are easy.
The elbow is actually the easiest.
Yeah.
What is it?
Face.
Chest.
So who gets the mouth?
Mouth and foot haven't come up yet.
You two are the mouth and the foot.
You two must be the mouth and the foot.
Definitely the mouth and the foot.
Only the foot and one other part left.
Who's the mouth?
Do you want the foot, or should I?
Pick one.
Knee.
Foot, here I come.
It's actually the mouth.
Mouth.
Come on.
Get ready for the baptism of my butt!
By then it'll have mixed together
armpit, elbow, knee, and butt smells.
All of it gets mixed up in your mouth.
Come on, three, two, one, go.
Three, two, one, go.
Actually, my collarbone didn't touch him.
No good.
Squat down first.
Okay, squatting down.
Okay.
Take it slow.
Wait a sec.
Slowly.
Stick your butt out a little more.
Right, good.
From my point of view, watching you two...
Take it slow.
Come over.
Come over, elbow.
Okay.
How am I supposed to get over there?
You can use both elbows.
No need to use just one.
Come over, a bit closer.
Wait a second, this is a little risky.
It's coming out, wait.
It's coming out.
Hey, can you speak properly?
What do you mean, "it's coming out"?
What kind of language is that?
What's coming out?
It's here.
Quick, bring your face over.
There.
Come on.
Where is it?
Right here.
Okay, is it clamped?
Hold on.
Wait a second.
Got it clamped.
Come on.
Okay.
So slippery.
Clamped it.
The ballet teacher.
Are you sure?
Let's both go lower.
Lower.
Even lower.
A bit higher.
So cold.
From my angle
it looks like he's licking his leg hair.
Xiaomeng is...
Those three are moving.
So many people?
Then how do I bite it?
How do I suck on it?
I want to join in.
So it's the four of us?
Xiaomeng, that's enough.
Xiaomeng, let go.
I can't bite it, it's too slippery.
Can this mouth stick?
I'm telling you, my mouth can't stick.
Just let it melt in your mouth.
My thigh's cramping.
We're done.
No.
It's fine.
Okay, challenge failed.
Time's up.
You know what?
That ice cube smelled awful.
It tasted salty.
And all kinds of other smells too.
The taste is Guorui's leg.
That ice cube has lots of weird flavors.
Come on, let's do this.
Let's pick one more time.
We'll give you one more chance.
Decide on the order.
Come on.
Don't be nervous.
Chest.
Butt.
Face.
Butt and face.
I'm butt, he's face.
No, wait.
Knee.
What?
So I'm serving you guys on my knees now?
I'm serving you two on my knees.
What did you get?
Face.
A warm face pressed against a cold butt.
Collarbone.
Foot.
Who's gonna get the mouth?
There's still the foot, worse than butt.
We're done.
Oh my. Who's gonna get the mouth?
I've been wearing
Weixian's height-boosting insoles.
Did nobody get the mouth?
Which one will be the mouth?
I'm face.
Foot to face.
No, we're done.
I haven't changed newly-washed socks.
I'm sorry, guys.
Mingyang, let's swap back.
I'm not going last anymore.
I don't want to. I'm fine here.
I'm doing just fine here.
Chest.
Come on, three, two, one, go.
Come on.
Don't move.
This is terrifying.
How can I move? How am I supposed to move?
Wait, how do you expect me to move?
Chen Zhixuan.
This thing won't go in.
My butt.
It's so cold.
I can't catch it.
Okay.
Who's next?
Wait, face and butt just can't catch it.
Hurry.
Keep going.
Again.
Wait a second.
I know.
Right, stick it up a bit higher.
One more time.
This is so hard,
his butt is all wet.
Get a shot of this.
All soaked.
Like he wet the bed.
Quick, get the ball.
Get up a little.
No, this pose is way too awkward.
Wait.
Then how do I catch it?
You catch it.
Quick, press it up.
How can I get up?
Slide down.
It fell into the butt crack.
Get up, get up a little.
You start over.
I'm starting over.
You get up.
I feel like I don't need my face pressed to a foot.
This is so hard.
Let's take a break.
It's too hard.
Come on, there we go.
That hurts.
Wait, I can't hold it at all.
I can't clamp it.
There's no room on his butt.
It's a flat surface.
How do I clamp it with my face?
I'll move you up a bit.
Clamp it, stick it into that butt crack.
No way, this one's impossible.
Too hard.
Try another one. Can't do it.
Too hard, we're giving up on this one.
No way, my butt can't get wet for nothing.
We surrender.
We're not doing this one.
After all these days this is our first time giving up.
Well then,
you can just adjust the order ourselves.
So it's still these same ones, right?
Yep.
Then chest is still first.
Hurry, someone pass it with their chest.
The feet definitely have to go last.
Okay, first one.
The first one is chest.
Chest, come on.
You're the chest, right?
You're the chest.
Okay, second is collarbone.
Collarbone, come on.
Taller ones to the later.
No, leave the last one for the feet.
Leave it for the feet.
Save the last one for the feet.
Okay, you two are the face.
What are you?
I'm butt.
Butt. You?
Butt. I'm the feet.
Feet. We're a perfect match.
I'm the knee.
Let him clamp it with his face to me.
Then I clamp it into your butt crack.
Then he clamps it over with his foot.
What do you mean, "into my butt"?
Can't you press it with your butt crack?
Clamp it with your butt crack.
That works too, actually.
You know, like squeezing a turd?
Let's give it a try, come on.
Come on.
Sphincter training today.
Three, two, one, go.
Come on, quick, keep going.
Keep going.
Lower down.
Clamp it like this.
Right.
Come on.
Actually, the face could go lower too.
See, there's a slope here.
Got it clamped.
Nice.
Who? Xiaomeng?
Me.
Chest.
Come on.
Don't move.
Okay.
I think it works.
I don't think so.
It's slid inside me already.
Let me hold your clothes.
Right, the clothes.
Okay.
Let go.
Okay, I've got it held down.
I'm holding the clothes down.
Who can help me fix my clothes?
Can someone give my clothes a tug?
Right.
So cold.
Just leave it like that.
Go ahead.
Don't move.
As long as you pull fast enough.
Don't move, what's next?
My knee.
It's the knee.
You two, squat down.
Squat a bit lower, you two.
Right, squat and catch it with your knees.
Mine.
Got it.
Head back, lean back.
Lean your head back.
Lie down and catch it with your knees.
Lie down slowly.
Slowly, lie all the way down.
Don't let it drop.
Lie down.
Clamp it with your foot.
How do I lie down?
Don't move.
I'm lying down.
Lie down slowly.
Good.
This hand up, this hand down.
What are you doing?
Okay.
Butt down, come on, butt.
Butt.
Quick.
Stick your butt out.
Butt.
Butt, right on the butt.
What?
Half, half is fine too.
Half.
Keep going.
There's half.
Okay.
Sit on him.
Sit on his knees.
Come on, sit up here.
Butt down.
How do I sit?
Again, I think it'll work.
Come on, one more time.
Keep going.
Quick.
Wait, get up.
How do I do this?
Come on, get up there.
On the butt, quick.
Alright, game failed.
Flailing for our lives, what is this?
I don't want to play anymore.
It's gone.
No more playing.
Let's just call it quits.
Who came up with this game?
Oh my god.
Now the next game is called
Rolling Balloon.
In this game,
we'll win back our dignity, okay?
Is there really any dignity left?
The eight students will pair up in twos
making four groups in total.
Two people hug each other and roll.
Within one minute,
pop the balloons on the mat
and you'll win our snack pack.
Let's start forming teams freely now.
Okay, I've got my team.
Clinging like a little bird.
Our heights match well, right?
We're a good height match.
Good, that's perfect.
Alright, then you and me.
We've already teamed up.
Isn't that how it is?
Right, so that's us.
Let's start rolling.
Let's draw lots instead.
Okay, come on, first group.
Three, two, one, go.
Gathering strength?
Impressive.
There's one more.
It's at the leg.
Pop!
Okay, twenty-two seconds.
It's not as easy as you think.
Let me tell you,
and it's not as pretty as we imagined.
Something's stuck in your butt crack.
How is this thing still stuck on here?
There's glue on it.
Three, two, one, go.
Go.
See, he had to brace himself too.
Did it pop?
Not popped.
Popped.
He did it with his knee.
I think using the knee works too.
They're fighting, the two of them.
Twenty-one point four eight seconds.
Great.
Three, two, one, go.
Come on.
So fast.
Good.
That was so fast.
Ten seconds.
Really fast.
Impressive.
So what now?
Ready, three, two, one, go.
What are you two doing?
They look like they're fighting.
Congrats on a fifteen-second time.
Congratulations to all four teams
for completing the game objective.
Please welcome Sun Mingyang as the representative
to come get your snacks.
I want the cheese sticks.
Then I'll take an Oreo.
Here, look, this one's for you.
It's your favorite.